Merry & Bright is a tv movie, romance film directed by Gary Yates.
Cate, CEO of the Merry and Bright Candy Cane Company,
meets Gabe during the busy Christmas season.
She assumes Gabe is the suitor her well-meaning mother is trying to set her up with when in reality, he works for Empire Corporate Recovery,
which has been hired to take a closer look at Merry and Bright's operation and find ways to make the company more profitable.
As Cate and Gabe begin to work together, they find ways to elevate the business
and find that they have more in common than savvy business sense.
Cate Merriwether, played by Jodie Sweetin.
Gabe Carter, played by Andrew W. Walker.
Joy Merriwether, played by Sharon Lawrence.
Sophie, played by Stephanie Moroz.
Pete, played by Darren Martens.
Sara Carter, played by Nancy Sorel.
Kellie Denise Bright (born 1 July 1976) is an English actress.
Her roles include Linda Carter in the BBC soap opera EastEnders, for which she won the 2015 British Soap Award for Best Actress and Best Dramatic Performance,
Julie in Ali G Indahouse, Joanna Burrows in The Upper Hand (1990–1996), Cassie Tyler in Bad Girls (2002) and Joan Trotter in Rock & Chips (2010–2011).
In 2015, she was the runner-up in the 13th series of
the BBC One show Strictly Come Dancing.
The tone is emotional.